I'm on a journey out to see the
world While I'm on my own I've
yet to reach the end So won't
you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon, the rain
will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the
anchor, now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm the storm
that you have built within.
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up,
we set stuff cause we can't.
Thresh enough, stand tall and
take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me wanna see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story.
Most will believe.
Not me.
Come and see.
I am on a journey.
Out to sea.
The world done on.
On my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now, right now.
Oh yes, we can.
The Great Master Cat Viper.
I just know you're going to love him.
I feel it in my bones.
In fact, I like him so much that I
decided to write a little song about him.
Let's go meet Master Cat Viper.
He will know what to do.
Let's go meet Master Cat Piper.
Let's go meet Master Catbifer.
He will know what to do.
Nami, we found no traces of Sanji.
Or cedar—what happened?
Did they take him against his will?
Well, no—he chose to go.
Wanda carrot,
it's hard I know, but
this is their business;
just let it go for their sake.
I'll take care of Peck homes here
too—let's not worry the daytime folks.
If we don't have to,
thank you guys; really,
come now—your crew displayed great compassion
for our people in their time of need;
we really should be thanking you,
gala—is that about the tommy?
I see.
Oh, the master is a
lonely man.
Yes, it's sad but true.
If I had a heart
inside of these ribs,
it would break in two.
Oh, the master keeps a
vigil at night, trying not to cry.
As
he looks up at
the sparkling moon, with a star in his
eye.
Still the master bears his
powerful fangs.
As he waits for the sun,
standing guard to help the
people he loves—till the night is done.
What
a nice song!
is done
What a nice song Is Cat Viper
really such a romantic character?
Oh, no, decidedly not.
Well, then what was the point?
It's just a song or something.
A wedding?
Are you sure he's gonna go?
I mean, going to see
girls is, like, his thing.
I guess he could have
meant something else.
It's just, he really seemed
like his mind was made up.
Well, maybe he'll come back with Mrs.
Sanji. Luffy!
What then we'd have a new Gourmet.
The trouble is the bride
is an emperor's daughter,
so if this union takes place, we'll
become big mom subordinates huh!
No way!
Well, that appeared to be the
way Sanji felt about it too;
he refused them without
a moment's thought,
but then that's troubling in
itself if he couldn't turn down
the wedding invitation because
of who he's dealing with—what?
You suppose he's going to do?
He must have some idea;
he's probably planning to uh, oh no!
I think I know what's up—he doesn't
want to put his crewmates in danger,
so he's gonna find a
way to separate from us.
Sanji quitting the straw
hats—that's the worst idea
ever—but that does make sense
now that I think about it.
He could have easily escaped when
he tossed us out, based on the way
the note was worded; I think he'd already
made his decision to go alone, idiot!
He's marrying big mom's
daughter, huh?
Forget about getting cold feet!
I'd be dead from hypothermia.
Same here!
And you said he's part of
the Vinsmoke family, right?
Sounds like they're probably
the key of solving this mystery.
I don't know his mom or his dad,
or if he has siblings or
what—all I know is that they
moved from the north blue to
the east blue a while back,
and now they live in the new world.
They've really done some
traveling over the years.
Then smoke—I believe that I've heard
of them. I feel terrible; I wish we
could
have kept him from
leaving until you guys got there,
but it was so quick at the end of the day.
Sanji made his own choice;
there was nothing you could have
done, so don't blame yourself.
I know, but either way—what if that
was the last time we'll ever see Sanji?
That'd be just fine with me!
Hey no! Really!
If he was gonna leave the crew forever,
don't you think the letter should have
said thank you guys for everything,
and he should have apologized for?
everything and he should have apologized
for for being such a pain in the ass.
Zoro, that's not the point at all!
Think about this.
We're like an unstoppable
train heading for disaster.
Remember what Caesar said about Smile?
When Doflamingo was dealing
those artificial devil fruits,
his biggest trade partner was Kaido.
Doflamingo was pissed when we
destroyed the lab back on Punk Hazard.
And then we destroyed
the factory on Dressrosa.
So the next guy who's gonna get upset
is the Emperor Kaido.
We can't ignore this
guy now that we're here.
We've already butted heads with the
Beast Pirates, and they answer to him.
Jack, the guy who wrecked
this place, is a threat too.
Only a matter of time
before they come for us.
The reason we allied with
Traffy is for the battle ahead.
I don't know why, but I think Kaido's
also got it out for Kin'emon and his pals.
Like it or not, we're gonna have to
go toe-to-toe with him pretty soon.
We were already in hot
water with one Emperor.
Leave it to that idiot
Curly Browse to throw
another one into the mix
and make things worse.
That's an awful way to look at this!
You're dumber than you look!
Those two things may be bad,
but they're not related, okay?
Say what you will.
That he never should have gotten himself
wrapped up in something
as stupid as matrimony.
What'd you say?
Now he's done it.
Please try not to get too heated, you too!
Who are you to decide that?
It's not your place to say if
someone else's problem is stupid!
Touchy!
Okay, if we can't figure it out, then
we'll just have to go and ask Sanji!
Huh?
Forget it.
Bad idea, Luffy. You're crazy.
We're just going to waltz
right up to Big Mom?
Yeah, we gotta go. I'm sorry.
You might have forgotten this,
but she does not like you.
No offense, but we can't beat her with just
our crew, especially with your strategy.
She's one of the four emperors.
Please, don't be reckless.
We've never faced anyone this strong.
Right, we gotta be sneaky.
And how are we supposed to do that?
Now that I think of
it, I might know a way.
There's a way, indeed.
You may not know which direction Big Mom's
subordinates headed
after taking Sanji away,
but they did leave someone behind
who's certain to be very knowledgeable.
Ergo, if that person is awake right
now, he can tell us something helpful.
Let's keep riding.
We'll see him shortly.
Holy crap, somebody
sure trashed this place.
The whale tree, it was already neat,
but from up close it's so cool!
Hey look, they're here!
The Straw Hat crew!
Oh yeah, there's Chopper!
Crush!
Crush buddy!
They're smiling.
Seems like they're bouncing back quick.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy, it's us!
Sorry about the fight before.
We're supposed to stop invaders
no matter who they are!
Oh, I know you!
Don't worry about it!
Anyway, is that cat guy around or what?
So our saviors are here!
We welcome you, Karoo and your friends.
Please allow me to express
our gratitude once more.
Who's up there?
I'm sorry, my men attacked you, Karoo.
They were merely acting out of
an abundance of caution. Huh?
Were you there indeed?
I saw it from the trees.
Go, see Beppo he.
and the rest of his group
are waiting in the back.
We will.
But not right now, okay?
We want to talk to the Cat
Viper and the Lion Viper first.
Crush!
If you're referring to Peccoms, he's up.
Go to the back building.
But be quiet.
We're keeping that
whole incident a secret.
Sanji is a good man.
We'll do whatever we can to help him out.
Luffy!
I'm worried about Cat Viper
in more ways than one,
So why don't I go check on him first?
Sure. Come, Doctor.
Please let me escort you, Tia.
Oh, Chopper, you feeling okay?
Uh-oh, me?
I sure am.
I've never been better.
It doesn't look that way.
Just follow me.
Sure.
Master Cat Viper is a little busy.
He's taking a bath.
A bath?
Meow, meow, meow, meow!
Lasagne-ow!
Get in my meow!
Tay, what's the matter with you?
You can't take a bath.
Your wounds will reopen.
And you need to eat lightly.
How are you even holding that spoon?
Are you listening?
Oh, chopper.
Not to worry.
I'm feeling great.
Not just that, but I
don't like taking orders.
At least take doctor's orders.
Wow, he's bigger than I thought.
Like it or not, I don't have to listen.
Oh, there.
It's my choice. My.
I can't get used to not having a left paw.
I can't even clap.
How sad is that?
Wait, who's here?
Oh, I know you gotta.
The great Straw Hat Pirates, huh?
You're the ones who saved me.
I'm grateful.
One day, I promise I'll
repay your kindness.
And I always keep my word.
I'm as driven as a man can be.
Huh? A ball?
Uh, uh, meow!
Ooh, yay, time to play!
I told you to rest, you big baby!
See that?
Your wound opened up!
Let me make one thing abundantly clear.
I got in bed because I wanted to,
not because I was feeling weak.
Yeah, yeah, sure. I get it.
Whatever makes you stay still.
Here comes a shot, okay?
Hey, you gotta, that
foxtail, wave it in my face.
Like this?
Woo-hoo, Fluffy!
Meow, meow.
Now, Chopper,
go ahead and give me the shot while
I'm enjoying this little distraction.
I would if you stopped moving!
You're afraid of a little needle?
Come on now!
I'm completely cured.
If there was a drug that good, I'd
have knocked you out with it by now!
Let's not hit injured people!
This big Fall sure tickles my funny bone!
Oh, I just love him!
I can't believe you survived that!
Of course I did!
My ability blocked half
of this attack! Get out!
That bastard Buggy!
I'm sorry I failed.
Your pal Blackleg is probably long gone.
Nowhere he's ever getting out
of that wedding ceremony now.
Who is it that's trying
to make him get married?
Sanji would never pick just one girl.
There was an agreement
made between our mama
and the patriarch of the Vinsmoke family.
Do you mean Sanji's father?
So what kind of a person is he?
He's got quite a reputation
in the underworld.
Are you familiar with
a group who goes by the
name of Germa Double Six aka the
warmongers? I've heard. Of them?
Sure, but they're an evil army
from a fairy tale, aren't they?
They're not real.
You're wrong.
That organization's as real as you or I,
and the Vinsmoke family sits
at the top of it, not only.
Only that, their leader happens to
be your pal Black Lake's father.
I want you all to know this.
I never meant to hide anything
from my friends, okay?
If you heard anything about them, you
probably know the Vinsmooks are bad news.
They're a vicious group of assassins.
Sanji is from a family of assassins?
I don't know what you're talking
about, and I don't care either.
Get out.
I expected as much.
Only one thing matters here.
Is Sanji coming back to us or not?
It doesn't matter to
me if he gets married.
But listen,
if you think that means we're going to
work under Big Mom, then you're crazy.
I'm fine with making an alliance,
but you guys got to work under us.
Do I need to call the doctor back?
You're so funny, Loopy!
You better watch that tongue,
brat, because I'll rack you! Gecko!
I owe you guys an all,
but don't push your luck.
Mama's an emperor, you know?
And you want to be the boss? Mm-hmm.
I need a timeout.
Your little eyeballs are funny.
Shut it!
Well, either way, he's not getting
out of this marriage. Why not?
Black Lake had the right
idea of giving himself up.
No one can turn down an invitation
to one of Mama's tea parties,
no matter what the reason might be.
Nobody puts Mama to shame,
not without paying the price.
A couple of days after they
don't show up at the party,
Mama's would-be guest
gets a surprise present.
I assure you it's the last
thing anyone would want.
They get a box with a loved
one's decapitated head in it.
It might be one of your heads if Mama
saw fit to hunt your crewmates down.
Or maybe it'd be the head
of one of Black Lake's
old pals from the
restaurant in the East Blue.
Or she could kill someone in the
Kamabaka kingdom who trained him.
Hold on.
How do you guys even know
all this stuff about Zod?
This is what true power can accomplish.
You get it?
That's what they must have told him.
There's no hope.
Cause you know when someone as strong
as Mama makes a threat like that.
She's gotta follow through with it.
That's why everyone bows down to her.
That's why no one can fight
against the four emperors.
It's the weight of absolute power that
brings even the strong to their knees.
Sanji knew the stakes.
He didn't go by choice.
One more thing maybe
this will put you at ease
for what it's worth once
this plays out you won't
be forced to work onto
Mama get out this marriage
is strictly political
if Mama wants someone
to be part of her crew
she wants them to be
part of her bloodline as
well in other words this
marriage is ritual to
forge a bond between the
Vinsmoke family and the
Charlotte family that's all
so from this point on
it's got nothing to do
with you guys you really
want me to spell this out
for you from the moment
that this marriage goes
off Black Lake Sanji will
no longer be a member of.
with the Straw Hat crew.
What kind of stupid rule is that?
Sanji's my friend, OK?
Yeah, but he's the son of the
Vinsmoke family before that.
And don't get mad at me. Get out.
There's no way Sanji would
agree to a marriage like that.
Even in the face of Mama and
the vicious Vinsmoke family?
All right.
But I doubt he'll live long
enough to tell the tale.
What do you know?
Actually, wait a sec.
What are you going to do after this?
As soon as I'm feeling up to
it, I'm going back to Mama.
Beyond that, I still got to settle
things with that damn Buggy.
He'll be surprised to see I'm not dead.
All right.
You can take me with you.
Luffy?
Listen, I'm going without you.
I'm with Robin on this one.
If we go together, it'll be like
we're trying to start a war.
We don't have time to be
getting into a big fight.
It's the only way.
If I stick with this guy,
I can crash the party.
All I need to do right now
is stop Sanji's wedding.
Hey, screw you!
I'm not gonna harbor an enemy
just because you say so!
This sounds like fun!
Carrot, no.
This isn't some joke.
Okay, so it's a deal.
What? No!
Hold the chopper, he'll heal you fast!
I never agreed to anything!
I'm not done with you!
Get back here!
Oh, Zoro, hey!
You hear about the wedding stuff?
Yeah, a little.
You're worried about Sanji too, aren't ya?
You want me to cut you?
I'm the one who said we
should forget about him.
Hey!
Luffy, Zoro, how's
Peckham's? Everything okay?
Oh, good, you're here.
Peckham's is bleeding a
lot and yelling and stuff.
Banging his head a bunch, too.
Better fix him quick.
Those are some serious symptoms.
I'll check him out.
Got you, Baron Corbett!
Ah!
Hey, there.
You gotta must be Straw Hat Luffy, huh?
I've been eager to meet you, gotta.
Aw, jeez!
Why are you out of bed again?
You're injured!
Not anymore!
I'm all better now!
That's not how it works!
He's huge!
So that's Cat Viper, huh?
He's a monster cat!
That's right!
Meow, meow, my meow!
A thank you, Crush!
Huh?
He's got double fountains of blood!
If you want to guard you
to death, do it without me!
Stay with us, Cat Viper, please!
What's going on here?
He'll need another transfusion.
Can you bring me some blood?
Whatever you need, Dr.
Chopper.
Oh, yes, uh, doctor, that's me.
Chopper, you okay?
Come on, cat, get up. We're gonna fight.
Hey, whoa, he's in bad shape.
Hey, Chef.
Whoa, is that your crew with you?
That's right, they wanted to meet you.
These are the Heart
Pirates, 20 members strong.
Thanks for taking care
of our Captain Straw Hat.
No, Bear!
Let's talk in private.
Why you gotta disrespect us, huh?
We're not having a party.
And we're not friends.
We're strategic allies.
I'm done for.
You're kidding.
Blackleg agreed to Big Mom's plan?
Mm-hmm, and you all just
stood there and let it happen.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna go take him back.
It's no big deal.
So do you mind if we hold off
on fighting Kaido for a little?
Not really my call.
Any way around it, it's only a matter
of time before Kaido comes for us.
My original plan was to hide
out here in Zo for a while,
but now that they know
where we are, we're screwed.
They come back for us and
invade this country and
it's people will suffer and
it will all be our fault
Where'd they come from?
You're true.
You're pirates, but you're all so sweet.
Thanks you God for caring about us.
You've made us so happy.
We can't thank you, Tia, enough.
Pucci, what happened? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Well, whatever.
Okay, let's have a party!
Time for some barbecue!
I'm just trying to help you!
Hell yeah!
Oh, hell no!
It would appear that Luffy and the others.
have completely forgotten
about our situation,
so it falls upon us, mature
adults, to handle things properly.
Very true, but we can
intercept the problem,
uh, we just gotta keep those samurai out.
Besides, since Raizo isn't here,
there's no need for Kin'emon and Kanjuro
to enter the country in the first place.
I'm sure they're blameless in this matter.
But the whole city was destroyed
because of their friend.
Bring Raizo to me or face destruction!
Where is the Wano Warrior?
They were so kind to us even
after all they've been through.
So we can't let them find out
that we're friends with samurai.
It might just break their
fluffy little hearts.
Or worse,
they find out that Kin'emon and his bros
were going to use this place as their.
rendezvous point.
These minks are kind-hearted folks,
but that would piss anyone off.
Last thing I want is to
fight with our new pals.
They've suffered enough.
It might not be much fun,
but we got to make sure those samurai
don't sneak in and ruin everything.
Well, I would scarcely call it record time,
but we've made it before dawn at least.
The trial is over.
At long last, our courage has won the day.
This has been quite the
misadventure, though, honestly.
The others must be quite worried about us.
I do hope they're in good health.
I feel a bit guilty.
Well, we shan't keep
them waiting much longer.
What a fine tiger you
are, Torosaburo A tiger?
Yes, of course, a tiger.
The color threw me off a bit.
And yet we must all say goodbye.
My dear monkey fellow.
Please pardon my rudeness.
But you have yet to answer our inquiry.
I must know if a warrior
named Race can be.
It's not this monkey's business!
Why are you perspiring
so profusely, my friend?
What's the matter?
Why do you flee?
We require your assistance
in finding Race.
Yes, monkey fellow!
You must be our guide!
This is Bananas!
Samurai have appeared!
I have to report this!
Samurai have come to zone!
You